{
    "subject": "resource/Louis_Gerhard_De_Geer",
    "predicate": "property/order",
    "object": "resource/Minister_for_Justice_(Sweden)",
    "human_readable": "Louis Gerhard De Geer was in the order of Minister for Justice (Sweden).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9653650522232056,
            "question": "In what country was Louis Gerhard De Geer a Minister for Justice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9186155796051025,
            "question": "What time period did Louis Gerhard De Geer serve as Minister for Justice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8997076749801636,
            "question": "What was the title of Louis Gerhard De Geer's role in Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8741270303726196,
            "question": "What position did Louis Gerhard De Geer hold in Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373309373855591,
            "question": "Was Louis Gerhard De Geer a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.832472562789917,
            "question": "What specific area was Louis Gerhard De Geer responsible for as a Minister?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7741944789886475,
            "question": "What is the significance of Louis Gerhard De Geer's role in Swedish history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6980725526809692,
            "question": "Did Louis Gerhard De Geer serve in other political roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747454404830933,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with Louis Gerhard De Geer's time as Minister?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6743855476379395,
            "question": "To which governmental branch did Louis Gerhard De Geer belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis Gerhard De Geer was in the order of Minister for Justice (Sweden).",
            "html": "dbpedia_2078_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements associated with Louis Gerhard De Geer's time as Minister?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2078_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Louis Gerhard De Geer serve in other political roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2078_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of Louis Gerhard De Geer's role in Swedish history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2078_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2078_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Baron Louis Gerhard De Geer was a Swedish minister of justice, and he held the office from April 7, 1858 to June 3, 1870."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Baron Louis Gerhard De Geer held positions including \"Prime Minister of Justice\" and \"Minister of Justice,\" which supports the statement that he was in the order of Minister for Justice in Sweden."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}